紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   國士章魚X
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   肉松
翻譯   吃冰棒
翻譯   煮粥
翻譯   WalkingNerd
翻譯   沫沫
翻譯   蘇小黛
時間軸   西·查
時間軸   王者蔥
時間軸   Jessie
后期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
校對   草草
總監   草草
紙牌屋
人人影視傾情奉獻
第五季  第七集
湯姆·漢默施密特
《華盛頓先驅報》
肝癌互助小組
安東尼·莫雷蒂紀念基金
本人  克萊爾·黑爾·安德伍德
I, Claire Hale Underwood,
在此莊嚴宣誓
do solemnly swear.
州長  我們剛剛聽說
Governor, we just got word
副總統克萊爾·安德伍德
that Vice President Claire Underwood
已宣誓就任代總統
was sworn in as acting president.
您知道嗎
Were you aware?
大家就問到這里吧
Uh, no further questions, everybody.
州長還要和國會議員們會面
The governor's here to talk to members of Congress.
非常感謝各位  謝謝
Thank you so much. Thank you.
南極洲麥克默多研究站
The McMurdo Research Facility in Antarctica.
佩特羅夫認為美國政府現在無暇他顧
Petrov thinks the US government has their eye off the ball.
他想錯了
Well, it doesn't.
你根本不明白  是吧
You have no idea, do you?
你在這里沒有分量了
No one hears you walking the halls of this building...
現在沒有了
not anymore.
我們獲勝的可能性有多大
What are our chances?
田納西和俄亥俄的重投是他的最佳機會
The revote in Tennessee and Ohio is his best shot.
每次失足都被強調  放大
Every misstep is highlighted and heightened.
他們想知道選舉到底怎么回事
They wanna know what happened with their election.
麗薩·威廉姆斯
Lisa Williams.
-她和瑞秋·波斯納  -打住
- She and Rachel Posner - Stop.
別再扯這些關于死去姑娘的陰謀論了
No more conspiracy theories about dead girls.
我手上有料
I have something.
或者說有你們想要的人
Or rather, someone you need.
你的艾丹·麥卡倫
Your Aidan Macallan.
他在這里  就在克里姆林宮里
He's here. In the Kremlin.
如果我們遂了他的愿
If we give him what he wants...
如果我們按厄舍的意思任命法官  那就完了
If we give Usher what he says, his justice, that is it.
徹底完了  我們就被他拿住了
It's over. He owns us.
-別小題大做  -是倒好了
- Don't exaggerate. - I wish I were.
這樣的交易你做過上千次了
You've made a thousand deals.
這次不一樣
Yeah, well, this one is different.
-怎么不一樣  -因為我能感覺到
- Why? - Because I can feel it right here.
-你聽見自己在說什么了嗎  -清清楚楚
- Do you hear yourself? - Yeah, loud and clear.
我倒有點奇怪你似乎一個字都沒聽見
I'm a little confused that you don't seem to hear me at all.
只要我們真正奪回權力
Once we're solidly back in power,
-我們就能恢復職位...  -幼稚
- we will regain our position... - That is naive.
你從來沒這么幼稚過
Naive is new for you.
我這是現實  不是幼稚
Realistic. Not naive.
我們奮斗的一切成果  都會煙消云散
Everything we've worked for, we can kiss it goodbye.
我們同意讓厄舍來挑人  沒得商量
We agreed to Usher's pick. It's non-negotiable.
說得太對了  他挑人  他的法官
That's exactly right. It's his pick. It's his justice.
他想控制我們的政府  我們的白宮
He's trying to control our house. The White House.
我向他保證過了  弗蘭西斯
I gave him my word, Francis.
你保證
Your word?
你保證  這場談話真是毫無意義
Your word? This conversation is pointless.
成熟點吧
Grow up!
你以為你是誰
Who do you think you are?
我以為我是臨時代總統
I think I am a temporary president
想幫你奪回寶座
trying to get you back in office.
如果你不認為眼下是我們至關重要的關口
And if you don't think that we're at a critical juncture in the road,
那你真是錯得可悲
you are pathetically mistaken.
醒醒吧  克萊爾  醒醒吧
Wake up, Claire! Wake up!
這是歐洲東部時間今早
Recorded this morning EET
在大馬士革亞默克區拍到的
in the Yarmouk neighborhood of Damascus.
看來他在劍橋期間喜歡上吃巧克力了
Seems he developed a taste for chocolate while at Cambridge.
畫面上這位是艾哈邁德·艾哈邁迪
Smiling for the camera is Ahmed Al Ahmadi,
尤瑟夫的兄弟
Yusuf's brother.
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
我和尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪談了很久
I had a long conversation with Yusuf Al Ahmadi.
他們倆完全不像
They look nothing alike.
就是他
It's him.
艾哈邁德還在我們監控中嗎
Is Ahmed still in our sights?
-是的  -這個機會非常難得
- He is. - This is a rare opportunity.
我們應該趁機發動定點襲擊
We should seize the moment and make a targeted strike.
-總監  得了吧  -總統女士
- Director, please. - Madam President...
有什么問題嗎  將軍
Is there some issue, General?
艾哈邁德·艾哈邁迪不可能大老遠地
Ahmed Al Ahmadi didn't travel all the way
從他的據點跑到大馬士革就為了買糖吃
from his compound to Damascus to buy a candy bar.
他肯定要見什么人  我們應該查清是誰
He's meeting with someone. Let's find out who.
可這樣他可能會被我們驚動  就此消失
Unless we're detected, and he disappears for good.
可我們只要等一等
But if we wait,
就非常有可能了解更多哈里發國的情報
there's a huge potential to learn more about ICO.
它的成員  聯系人  行動規律和戰術
Its members, contacts, habits, tactics.
你今天早上真是一反常態地
You know, you're sounding uncharacteristically dovish
保守啊  將軍
this morning, General.
我同意布雷格將軍的看法
I agree with General Braegher.
雖然對艾哈邁迪發動精確空襲
While a successful air strike against Ahmadi
-會非常有利于  -這跟選舉無關  凱茜
- would play well... - This isn't about the election, Cathy.
當然沒關系  我是說  只要我們手段得當
No, of course not. I mean, if we do this correctly,
我們就可以逐步瓦解哈里發國的網絡
we can begin the process of dismantling ICO's network.
干掉他
Take him out.
如果總統同意的話
If the president agrees,
我認為這對國家最有利
I think it's the best thing for the country.
我覺得這會給哈里發國發出非常明確的信號
Well, I think it would send a very clear message to ICO.
短期來看沒錯  但是
In the short term, yes, but...
短期沒錯就夠了
No other term is relevant.
我覺得我們已經在
I think we have been operating
恐怖主義的陰影下忍受太久了
under the shadow of terror for too long.
為了美國人民  我們必須采取堅決行動
For the sake of the American people, we need to act now.
預計需要多長時間  將軍
What's the timetable, General?
只要目標位置準確  幾個小時就行
For an actionable location, most likely a number of hours.
謝謝
Thank you.
你這是在浪費我們的時間
You're wasting our time.
我們要講究他在哪以何種面貌出現
We're being selective about where and how he appears.
很快他就什么活動都不能參加了
Soon he won't be at any events at all.
漢娜  我們只是想盡力把他和你送入白宮
Hannal, we're just trying to land him and you in the White House.
不是布洛哈特-康威  馬克  是康威在前
And it's not Brockhart-Conway, Mark. It's the opposite.
他肯定忍不了多久
He won't put up with this much longer.
我知道他一定很難受
I know, I'm sure it's hard on him.
我得接這個電話  抱歉
I have to take this. I'm sorry.
他到那兒之后會怎么樣
What happens after he gets there?
-威爾會怎么樣  -我們會支持他
- To Will? What happens? - We'll be there for him.
-你和布洛哈特將軍  -對
- You and General Brockhart? - Yes.
威爾是什么角色
What will Will's role be?
我會繼續支持你丈夫
I will continue to support your husband.
給我一個真正的答案  你欠我的
Give me a real answer. You owe me that.
他的角色將是美國總統
His role will be President of the United States.
麥克風還開著  布洛哈特脫口而出
The mic was still hot and Brockhart just kept talking.
-她是這么說的  -抗命嗎
- That's what she said. - Insubordination?
-她用的是這個詞嗎  -她聽著是這意思
- That's the word she used? - It's what it sounded like to her.
他在談士兵  他說
He was talking about soldiers and he said, quote,
"我第一個站出來讓軍人抗命"
"I'll be the first to tell them not to listen."
-她能不能弄到真正的錄音  -是有代價的
- Can she get her hands on the actual clip? - For a price.
-我還以為她是朋友  -對  聰明的朋友
- I thought she was a friend. - Yeah, a smart friend.
這是一條很不錯的辯論后30秒廣告
It's a nice 30-second spot, post-debate.
如果有辯論的話
If there is a debate.
攻擊他們的長處
Hits them at their strength.
動搖他們的軍事公信力
Takes the military credibility away.
這種東西能反轉大選結果
This is the kind of thing that can turn an election.
不管要付出什么代價  都值了
Whatever this costs... it's worth it.
我們把它搞到手  證實一下
Let's secure it and then verify it.
不管是不是休會任命本森大法官
Recess appointment of Judge Benson or no,
得讓人們繼續關注田納西和俄亥俄的重新投票
people need to stay focused on the revote in Tennessee and Ohio
以及我們為何走到這一步
and how the hell we got here.
好
All right.
我讓助理安吉拉聯系你
I'll have my assistant Angela reach out
看你什么時候需要我去錄影棚
to confirm what time you need me at the studio.
好  好的
All right. Yep. Yeah.
我把道格·斯坦普被劫車那天
I collected everything I could find
能查到的資料都搜集齊了
about the day Doug Stamper was carjacked.
好
Good.
好了  那么
All right, so...
是在哪
where was that?
在哪發生的
Where that happened?
在馬里蘭
In Maryland.
就在
Right around, um...
我是在離那兒半小時車程的地方長大的
Yeah, I grew up about a half an hour from there...
在這里
It's here.
瑞秋·波斯納的
And Rachel Posner's...
最后已知地址
last known address.
也就15分鐘路程
I'd say they were about 15 minutes apart.
我不知道我為什么要跟你解釋
I'm not sure why I need to explain myself to you.
你為什么要去國安局
Why would you go to the NSA?
我想調查一名美國公民是否安然無恙
I was inquiring into the well-being of an American citizen.
他就是個心懷不滿的黑客而已
He's just a disgruntled hacker.
那你為什么對他這么感興趣呢
Then why are you so interested in him?
他看上去怎么樣
How did he look?
我是為了我自己問的
I'm asking for me.
我13歲就認識艾丹了
I've known Aidan since I was 13 years old.
他和我媽媽曾交往過幾年
He and my mom dated for several years.
當然  那是很久之前了
Was a long time ago, obviously.
但他并不想要國安局那份工作
But as far as the NSA job, he didn't want it.
是我逼他接受的
I made him take it.
我不明白他們怎么找到他的  他為什么在那兒
I don't understand how they got him or why he's there.
我需要知道他是安全的
I need to know that he is safe.
他看上去還行
He looked fine.
他知道什么  莉安
What does he know, LeAnn?
也許跟你我知道的差不多
Probably about the same as you and me,
所以我們不能讓他惹上嚴重的麻煩
which is why we need to keep him out of any serious trouble.
我不想涉足你的私生活  莉安
I don't want to get involved in your personal life, LeAnn.
-我是來見總統的  -當然
- I'm here to see the president. - Of course.
但你仔細想想  凱茜
But when you think about it, Cathy,
我們都脫不了干系
we're all sort of involved here.
如果他有危險  他是無法承受的
If he is in any kind of danger, he is not built for it.
你好  凱茜
Hi, Cathy.
簡
Jane.
莉安·哈維  簡·戴維斯  簡是副部長
LeAnn Harvey, Jane Davis. Jane is under secretary--
商務部副助理部長  負責國際貿易
Deputy under secretary of commerce for international trade.
很拗口
It's a mouthful.
很高興見到你本人
Yeah, it's good to put a face to the voice.
你有布洛芬嗎
Uh, do you have any ibuprofen?
-我好像有阿司匹林  -不行
- Oh, I might have some aspirin. - No.
-我過敏  會起疹子  -我們好像有
- I'm allergic. Gives me hives. - We may have some.
你家就是做輪胎的哈維家族  對吧
You're the Harveys of the tire company, yes?
我父親和叔叔二十年前賣了公司
My father and uncle sold the business 20 years ago.
之后胎面就不一樣了
And the treads haven't been the same since.
但很不錯  你還是來到了華府
But it's great. You finally landed in D.C.
我會告訴總統你們倆都來了
I'll let the president know you're both here.
謝謝你的藥
Uh, thank you for this.
我們對調這兩句就行了
Let's just reverse those two sentences and it's there.
切中要點
It's to the point.
-凝練  -沒錯  凝練
- Pithy. - Yes, pithy.
她們來了
Your meeting is here.
謝謝
Thank you.
本森法官正在前往
And Justice Benson is en route
白宮參與宣布儀式
to the White House for the announcement.
我會讓她在黃色橢圓廳等
I'll have her wait in the Yellow Oval.
好  讓她們進來  行嗎
Uh, great. Can you send the others in, please?
好的
Of course.
前總統也會去玫瑰園嗎
Is the former president meeting us in the Rose Garden?
弗蘭西斯不去
Francis will not be there.
他不必去
He's not needed.
戴維斯女士
Miss Davis.
杜蘭特國務卿
Secretary Durant.
-好久不見  -是啊  上次見面是在哪
- It's been a long time. - Yes, where was that?
阿斯彭一家智庫  2000年初
A think tank in Aspen, early 2000.
那時還有很多"智慧的火花"
Oh, there was a lot of thinking happening back then.
還好我們阻止了
I'm glad we put a stop to that.
請坐
Please, have a seat.
我看過了與北京的
So, I've gone over the numbers
鋼鐵協議的草案數據
of the proposed agreement of steel with Beijing
我有些問題想問你
and I have a couple of questions for you.
總統女士  我們需要帶你撤離
Madam President, we need to evacuate you now.
怎么回事
What's going on?
請撤離  總統女士  是緊急情況
Please, Madam President. It's urgent.
女士
Ma'am.
你們要帶我去哪
Where are you taking me?
-將您轉移到總統緊急行動中心  -為什么
- We're moving you to the PEOC. - Why?
他們會在下面告訴您  女士
They'll brief you down below, ma'am.
弗蘭西斯人呢
Where's Francis?
道格·斯坦普呢  還有耶茨先生呢
Where's Doug Stamper? And Mr. Yates?
我們在照章辦事  女士
We're following protocol, ma'am.
國家安全顧問卡弗蒂在路上了
National Security Advisor Cafferty is on her way.
-女士  -不  我們等弗蘭西斯
- Ma'am? - No, we'll wait for Francis.
他會在里面與您會合
He'll meet you inside.
我們要等弗蘭西斯  這是命令
We will wait for Francis. That's an order.
-總統女士  -卡弗蒂女士  怎么回事
- Madam President. - Miss Cafferty, what's going on?
尚無確切消息
Nothing's confirmed yet,
但一輛攜帶放射性物質的卡車失蹤了
but a truck carrying radioactive material has gone missing.
-這是真的嗎  -我們得和格林談談
- Is this real? - We have to talk to Green.
我們進去吧
Let's head inside.
是
Yes.
我明白了  謝謝
I see. Thank you.
國土安全部收到網絡司令部的消息
Homeland received word from Cybercom
一輛攜帶三臺銫137輻照器的卡車
that a truck carrying three cesium-137 irradiators
未按時到達兩個檢查站
missed two checkpoints.
卡車本該從亞特蘭大
It was supposed to be traveling from Atlanta
駛回巴爾的摩的生產廠商那里
back to the manufacturer in Baltimore.
卡車現在在什么位置
Where do we think the truck is now?
卡車的衛星定位下線了
Truck's GPS is offline.
怎么會出這樣的破事
How the hell does a thing like that happen?
-我們得重新評估  -可是該重新評估了
- We'll have to reevaluate. - You're damn right we will.
但我們必須作出決定
But we need to make some decisions.
我們應該通知特區警察和弗州州警
We should notify Metro PD and Virginia State Police.
要不要疏散群眾
Are we gonna evacuate the public?
不行  在采取任何行動之前
No. Before we do anything,
我要和反恐處局長談一談
I wanna speak to the head of counterterrorism.
給我接助理局長格林
Get Assistant Director Green on the line.
-女士  國安部已經  -總統說得對
- Ma'am, Homeland is over... - The president is right.
女士
Ma'am?
我是安德伍德總統
This is President Underwood.
眼下我們還不清楚誰對這起事件負責
At this time, we have no idea who's responsible.
格林局長  我最好還是
Director Green, perhaps it's better
把你接到免提上  請稍等
I patch you into the whole room. One second.
自從他的輪班開始  司機就失聯了
The driver's been unreachable since his shift began.
卡車上的放射物
There's enough radiation on that truck
足夠影響方圓50公里左右的區域
to impact a 30-mile radius.
即便不被武器化  也會擴散到大氣中
Even if it's not weaponized, it would be in the air,
水里  影響兒童和平民
in the water, children, people...
將軍  我在這里都能聽見車輪轟轟響了
General, I can hear the wheels grinding from here.
最好還是不要妄加推測  先生
I'd rather not speculate, sir.
請你盡情推測一下
Oh, please do.
過去幾天以來  哈里發國的情報越來越多
Over the past several days, there has been increased ICO chatter,
但這已經是新常態了
but that is the new normal.
我們把可能受影響區域的地圖和數據發過去了
We've sent over stats and maps of potentially affected areas.
我真不知道哪個更可怕
I don't know what's worse.
是隨時會炸的臟彈  還是全城人知道
A dirty bomb about to go off or what'll happen to the city
我們在找一枚臟彈后的反應
when they know we're looking for one.
-上頭有誰留守  -賽斯和莉安
- Who do we have left upstairs? - Seth and LeAnn.
你和格林保持通信
You stay in touch with Green.
如果真的有臟彈
If this is a dirty bomb,
那局面可就徹底不一樣了
then we've just entered a different world.
好  先生
Yes, sir.
好了  我們繼續集中力量
All right, we need to stay focused
制定一份緊急疏散計劃
on our contingency plan for an evacuation
但不要讓外界察覺我們的行動
without the appearance of doing so.
我們需要準備實施單向...
We need to be ready to implement one way...
給我聯系能源部的清理小隊...
We need to get the cleanup team from the Energy...
...有權調取安保監控錄像....
...whose jurisdiction it is to get the security cams...
沒錯  最終宣布后
Yes. Whenever it happens,
這次任命便能打破最高法院的僵局
this appointment would break the court's deadlock.
我們終于能繼續推進這次大選了
And we would get this election going again.
但請大家退一步想一想
But let's step back a minute.
田納西已經不重要了
Tennessee is out of the equation.
無論誰贏下田州  都不夠取勝
Whoever wins that state, it's not enough.
這樣就取決于最后一個州  俄亥俄州
It's come down to one state. Ohio.
一個州的選擇  將左右
One state is about to choose
下一任美國總統的人選
the next President of these United States.
我們怎么會讓這種事發生
How did we let this happen?
而且還不止一次
And it keeps happening.
這屆政府一貫喜歡搞閉門政治
This is an administration that operates behind closed doors,
逃避公共監督
out of the public eye.
今天的突然推遲也是一貫的套路
Today's sudden postponement is typical.
玫瑰園沒發表一個字的聲明
With no announcement in the Rose Garden,
整個白宮也完全沒有任何消息放出
and literally zero news coming from the White House,
我們不得不去想  究竟發生了什么幕后驚變
one has to wonder what is going on behind the scenes
才導致這次意外推遲
to cause this unexpected delay.
白宮的沉默  振聾發聵
The silence is deafening.
在這樣一場曠日持久
After such a protracted,
令人疑惑  混亂不堪的選舉之后
confusing and, frankly, chaotic election,
我們有權了解真相
we deserve clarity.
可是  又是這樣
Instead, here we are again...
我們又被蒙在鼓里  神經緊張
left out of the loop and on the edge of our seats.
我希望美國人民不會習慣了這種現象
I just hope America isn't getting used to this.
-喂  -是我
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.
道格
Doug?
為什么沒人告訴我
Why wasn't I read in?
-告訴你什么  -正在發生的事
- To what? - Whatever's going on.
如果總統躲入地堡會對我們有利
If this is gonna play for us, the president in the bunker,
我要知道該如何操作
I need to know how to play it.
有一輛運送
There's a truck carrying
放射性物質的貨車失聯了
radioactive material that's gone missing.
好  賽斯和我要準備一份聲明嗎
Okay. Should Seth and I prepare a statement?
-我們要說貨車在哪  -不清楚
- Where are we saying the truck is? - We don't know.
-什么時候能找到它  -也不清楚
- When are we gonna find it? - We don't know.
等下  真的有事發生嗎
Wait, is something really happening?
可能沒有
Probably not.
-喂  -可能沒有
- Hello? - Probably not?
那我該做些什么
What am I supposed to do?
-是道格嗎  -是的
- Is that Doug? - Yeah.
我能跟他說兩句嗎
Can I talk to him?
-你能告訴我們什么  -表現如常
- Hey, what can you tell us? - Act normal.
繼續關注情勢
Stay on point.
只回應正在進行的競選活動
Comment only on the ongoing campaign.
我已經把他們的日程活動延期了
I've already postponed their scheduled events.
我們現在有危險嗎
Look, are we in danger here or what?
我無法回答這個問題
I can't answer.
因為我也不知道
Because I don't know.
靜等國安部的進一步指示吧
Await further instructions from Homeland.
好吧
All right.
道格  我們還要留在這兒嗎
Doug, should we be here?
他掛了
He hung up.
我們在做什么
What are we doing?
諾拉覺得我們需要通知麥卡錫議長
Nora thinks we need to notify Speaker McCarthy.
我覺得現在談政府繼續運作為時尚早
I think it's too soon for a continuity of government.
如果我們計劃撤離  需要通知國會
If we're planning an evacuation, Congress needs to be notified--
我說了  我覺得太早了
I said, I believe it is a bit too early.
總統女士  莫里森總監認為...
Madam President, Director Morrison thinks that--
等下  莫里森總監在哪  為什么...
Wait a minute. Where is Director Morrison? Why--
她選擇留在國家情報總監辦公室
She opted to stay at ODNI.
她在那里指揮行動
She's monitoring from there.
至少給她打個電話
Well, at least let's get her on the phone.
我們早該在數月前趁有機會時鏟除哈里發國
We should have wiped out ICO when we had the chance.
我們沒問你的個人意見  將軍
We didn't ask for your personal opinion, General.
我們需要了解艾哈邁德·艾哈邁迪的最新情況
What we need is an update on the Ahmed Al Ahmadi situation.
是  女士  我這就去和莫里森總監確認
Yes, ma'am. I'll check with Director Morrison now.
我有一些關系
I have contacts, you know.
本地的私人承包商  也許能幫上忙
Private contractors in the region that might be of help.
你是暗示說你的聯系人
Are you suggesting that your contacts
比聯調局和國安局知道得還多嗎
know more than the Bureau, the NSA--
我沒有暗示什么
I'm not suggesting anything.
我是在告訴你
I'm telling you.
我認識和哈里發國談判過的第三方人士
I know third parties that have negotiated with ICO in the past.
人質之類的事  他們也許知道點什么
Hostages and whatnot... who may know something.
但我需要打個電話
But I need a line.
保密電話
Just a... a secure one.
我在這兒都快透不過氣了
I can barely breathe in here.
我去給咱們倒杯咖啡
I'm gonna go get us a cup of coffee.
戴維斯女士怎么會有這么高的安全等級
How does Miss Davis have this level of clearance?
這值得探究
That's a good question.
-我們是不是自作自受  -什么
- Did we bring this on ourselves? - What?
-對不起  我不該這么說的  -聽我說
- I'm sorry. I shouldn't have. - Listen to me.
我們所做的一切  一切
Everything we've done, everything,
都是我們必須做的
is exactly what we had to do.
我們都還不知道這是不是真的
We don't even know if this is real.
這是我在香港買的
I get these in Hong Kong.
最好喝的速溶咖啡出自環太平洋地區
The best instant coffee comes out of the Pacific Rim.
-你想來一杯嗎  -如果你還有多的
- Would you like one? - If you can spare it.
我包里總是裝著三四包
Oh, I always have three or four in my bag.
不知我們要在這里待多久
I wonder how long we'll be down here.
目前情勢還不明朗
The situation's still unclear.
我不該喝咖啡的  我還有點站不穩
I shouldn't be drinking coffee. I still feel a little shaky.
你看起來還好
You don't look it.
摸摸我的脈搏
Feel my pulse.
我看你很自若
You seem very much in control to me.
你也是
So do you.
這說明了我們什么
What does that say about the two of us?
好的  謝謝
Yes, thank you.
海豹突擊隊正在追蹤艾哈邁德·艾哈邁迪
The SEAL team is on the trail of Ahmed Al Ahmadi,
但是國家情報局認為
but National Intelligence believes
他發現我們在追蹤他了
he's discovered we're following him
而那卡車正是對策
and the truck is a countermeasure.
哈里發國想看到艾哈邁迪完好地走出大馬士革
ICO wants to see Ahmadi walking out of Damascus in one piece.
如果我們襲擊  他們會反攻
If we strike, they will hit back.
需要啟動首都撤離程序
Capital-wide evacuation procedures need to be initiated--
-等等  -我們得首要考慮民眾
- Just hold on! - No, the public is our priority--
等等  我想知道襲擊的可能性有多大
Hold on! I want to know how close we are to a strike
以及這輛該死的卡車在哪里
and where this goddamn truck is
然后我們再做最后的決定
before we make any final decisions.
"我們再做最后的決定"
"We make any decisions"?
沒錯  我仍然是
Yes, I am still in a position to make--
如果我錯了就糾正我  但你不是
Correct me if I'm wrong, but you are not in a position--
諾拉  敵人不在這里
Nora. The enemy isn't in here.
卡弗蒂說得對  我們應該撤離
Cafferty is right. We should evacuate.
但我想的是將軍
But it's the general who's on my mind.
卡弗蒂女士
Miss Cafferty.
我完全失態了  請接受我的道歉
I was entirely out of line. Please accept my apology.
我和戴維斯談過了
I spoke with Davis.
-怎樣  -一無所獲  她只是在耍滑頭
- And? - Nothing. She was just flexing.
凱茜
Cathy.
今天是誰安排了和克萊爾的會議
Who called a meeting with Claire today?
你還是戴維斯女士
You or Miss Davis?
是簡
Jane did.
非常感謝  凱茜
Thank you very much, Cathy.
-沒事了嗎  -是的  謝謝
- Was that all? - Yes, thank you.
抱歉  還有一件事
Oh, sorry, one more thing.
布雷格什么時候得到第四顆星的  哪屆政府
When did Braegher get his fourth star? Which administration?
幾屆前
A couple back.
他和布洛哈特是一起的嗎
So he and Brockhart together?
是的  還有幾位也在大概同一時期晉升
And a few others who were elevated around the same time, yes.
謝謝  凱茜
Thank you, Cathy.
我們談過的那個布洛哈特的料  你拿到了嗎
That Brockhart spot we talked about. You have it?
證實了嗎
Is it verified?
等等
Hold on.
好了
Ready.
我對天發誓
I swear to God,
要是安德伍德往邊境派兵
if Underwood puts soldiers on those borders,
我第一個站出來讓軍人抗命
I'll be the first to tell them not to listen.
如果美國總統下達那種命令
If the President of the United States gives orders like that,
你就讓他早死早超生
you put him out of his misery.
沒了  這是全部
That's it. That's all I have.
不  這很好
No, that's good.
如果我們撐過了今天
If we survive the day.
賽斯還和你在辦公室嗎
Is Seth still in the office with you?
我在總統辦公室  坐在堅決桌后
I'm in the Oval, sitting behind the Resolute desk.
你不會的
That's not you.
你總是對我下判斷
You know, you keep deciding who I am
卻總是誤判我
and you keep reading me wrong.
有關于這里發生了什么的謠言嗎
Are there rumors about what's going on down here?
有  但我們在應付了
Yes, but we're deflecting.
-康威競選團隊來問過嗎  -還沒有
- Has the Conway campaign reached out? - Not yet.
將軍在俄亥俄州做巡回宣傳  州長斷聯了
The general's on a stump in Ohio and the governor's off the grid.
-好的  繼續留意他  -我會的
- Okay. Stay on him. - I will.
除非是世界末日  那就沒關系了
Unless it's the end of the world and it doesn't matter.
再見  道格·斯坦普
Goodbye, Doug Stamper.
你確定你該進去那里嗎  金發姑娘
Are you sure you should be in there, Goldilocks?
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
坦白說  我在想我們在地下多深
Honestly, I was thinking about how far down we are
以及我不喜歡這樣
and how it's not my favorite thing.
對不起  你需要進來嗎
I... I'm sorry. Do... do you need to be in here?
不不  沒關系
No. No, no. It's fine.
我曾經害怕飛行  后來克服了
I used to have a fear of flying, but I got over it.
現在再也不怕了
Doesn't bother me at all anymore.
但我的恐懼似乎轉向了另一個方向
But the pendulum seems to have swung the other way.
如果我想太多  會開始有活埋感
If I think too hard, I start to feel buried.
不好意思  室內空氣循環讓我更加不安了
Forgive me. It's the recirculated air, makes things worse.
戴維斯女士  你為什么會來這兒
Miss Davis, why are you here?
-特勤局帶我來的  -不
- This is where the Secret Service led me. - No.
不管是否在準入名單上  你必定是自愿來的
Access list or not, you have to choose to be here.
我總是選擇最安全的地方
I always choose the safest place.
你為什么會來這兒
Why are you here?
感覺有機可尋
It felt like an opportunity.
會面的機會  私下會面
A chance for a meeting, not quite on the books.
我剛通完電話  總統女士
I just got off the phone, Madam President.
我有來自國外私人承包商的信息
I have information from abroad, from private contractors...
艾哈邁迪在大馬士革
Ahmadi is in Damascus.
多方勢力競相要捉住他
And a number of parties were racing to capture him,
其中當然包括美國
including, of course, the United States.
但是沒有人
But no one...
能在今天逮住他
will be capturing him today.
或是在選舉前逮住他
Or before the election.
我的職業
I've made a career...
就是處理世界的問題地區
out of dealing with problematic parts of the world.
我的工作  就是想象不可想象之事
It's kind of my vocation to imagine the unimaginable.
失陪了
Excuse me.
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Pardon me. - I'm sorry.
-沒事  -失陪了  總統先生
- It's all right. - Excuse me, Mr. President.
我感覺她想把艾哈邁迪獻給我們
I had the distinct feeling she was offering Ahmadi to us.
意思是
Meaning?
她說有多方勢力正在設法捉住他
She said there are a number of groups looking to capture him,
但在選舉之前都不會有人成功
but that no one will. Not today or before the election.
這是我們自找的
We brought this on ourselves.
-我們逼得太緊  -我們存活下來了
- We pushed too hard. - We've survived.
-我們自我孤立了  弗蘭西斯  -又如何
- We isolated ourselves, Francis. - So what?
你我都明白一件
We both know something
其他人拒絕承認的事
the rest of the world refuses to acknowledge.
世上沒有正義  唯有征服
There is no justice, only conquest.
我告訴你  我們要是準許他們疏散華盛頓
And let me tell you, we let them evacuate D.C.,
我們就沒戲了 克萊爾  我們就輸了
we are done, Claire. We've lost.
請進
Yes?
我剛和莉安通了話  你們得聽聽
I just spoke to LeAnn. You need to hear this.
我對天發誓
I swear to God,
要是安德伍德往邊境派兵
if Underwood puts soldiers on those borders,
我第一個站出來讓軍人抗命
I'll be the first to tell them not to listen.
如果美國總統下達那種命令
If the President of the United States gives orders like that,
你就讓他早死早超生
you put him out of his misery.
讓我出去
Let me out.
-很抱歉  先生  我不能...  -開門
- I'm sorry, sir. I'm not allowed-- - Open the door.
-我奉命...  -我已經不是總統
- My orders are to-- - I am no longer the president.
我已無義務或責任在身  是不是
I have no responsibilities or obligations. Isn't that correct?
解除威脅前我們不能讓你出去
We can't send you above until the threat is contained--
-把門打開  -讓他出去
- Open this door. - Let him out.
-女士  -讓總統出去
- Ma'am? - Let the president out.
把門打開
Open the door.
打開
Open it.
總統女士
Ma'am.
我們必須開始疏散
We need to initiate evacuation now.
不  將軍  我說疏散才疏散
No, General. We'll do it when I say so.
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我知道我答應你了  但我得去接我小孩
I know I agreed to do this, but I have to go pick up my kids.
沒事  要不我搭你的車
Okay. Well, what if I just rode in the car with you?
家長都在互相發信息
You know, parents are texting one another.
其中一位家長在國安局任職
One of them works at the NSA
他認為有恐襲的可能  所以...
and he thinks there's a terror threat, so...
這事以前也發生過  但...世事難料
I mean, this has happened before, but you just... You never know.
我母親上個月腎衰竭過世了
My mom died of kidney failure last month.
我很遺憾
Oh, I'm so sorry.
她在候捐名單上嗎
Uh, was she on the donor list?
有  但排得不夠靠前
Yeah, but not close enough to the top.
你介意嗎  我們可以邊走邊說
Do you mind? You could talk while we walk out of here.
好吧  好
Sure. Yeah.
安東尼病了多久了
Uh, how long was Anthony sick for?
大概兩年
About two years.
他一直在抗爭  非常頑強  直到最后
And he fought it hard. So hard. The entire way.
這地方  只要是現金支付  我就不多問
This unit, if they pay cash, I don't ask questions.
-但你記得那兩個年輕女子吧  -當然
- But you remember these young women? - Yeah, of course.
她們非常親密  如果你明白我的意思
They were very close, if you know what I mean.
但她們很可愛
But they were sweet.
那你有沒有見過這個人
And did you ever see... this man?
我不清楚究竟是怎么回事
Look, I don't know what was going on here.
但你認得他吧
But you recognize him?
認得
Yeah. Okay?
是有一個長這樣的人預付了三個月房租
Someone looking like him paid the rent. Three months, up-front.
但我說了  我不做評判
But like I said, I don't judge.
我不明白你問的是什么  總統先生
I'm not sure what you're asking, Mr. President.
得了吧
Oh, please.
某個人或者某些人
Someone or someones...
今天想把我和我夫人困在地下
tried to make my wife and I lose the election
好讓我們輸掉大選
by keeping us underground today.
我想知道你對此有什么了解
And I would like to know what you know about that.
我們都在實時應對
We've all been responding in real time
一起潛在的恐怖襲擊
to a potential terrorist attack.
但你選擇待在這里
But you chose to stay here.
你怎么不和我們一起去地堡
Why weren't you in the bunker with us?
我選擇留在我的辦公室
I chose to remain in my office
監督對艾哈邁德·艾哈邁迪的逮捕或擊殺
to oversee the capture or killing of one Ahmed Al Ahmadi.
但今天上午  你和布雷格將軍
And yet there was great tension this morning
鬧得很緊張
between you and General Braegher.
見解不同
Difference in approach.
我們不會疏散哥倫比亞特區的
We are not going to evacuate the District of Columbia.
我要你明白這一點  無論如何
I want you to understand that. Come what may.
另外我向你保證  凡妮莎
And I promise you this... Vanessa.
等我查明真相
When I find out exactly what has happened,
我會記得這次對話
I'm going to remember this conversation,
我會記得  你選擇了隱瞞信息
when you chose to withhold information.
布雷格將軍是布洛哈特將軍的強烈支持者
General Braegher is a strong supporter of General Brockhart.
他們串通了嗎
Did they conspire?
他們是不是想利用恐怖
Did they use... terror...
和此次疏散
and this evacuation
讓我輸掉這場大選
to cost me this election?
我并不喜歡將軍這個人
I'm not a fan of the general...
但這是個嚴重的指控
but... that's a strong charge,
而且沒有任何證據支撐
and there's no proof to support it.
你們這些人最擅長保護的  是彼此
You know, what you people protect best is each other.
艾哈邁迪不久前沒了蹤跡
We lost Ahmadi a short time ago
我們相信他已經不在大馬士革了
and believe he is no longer in Damascus.
當然了
Of course.
你聽好了
Now you listen to me...
這就是一次
This was nothing more or less
明明白白的政變未遂
than an attempted coup, plain and simple.
我不知道你直接參與的程度多深
And I do not know to what degree you have been directly involved.
但你必須化解它
But you will resolve it.
立即化解
Now.
聽明白了嗎
Do I make myself clear?
明白了  先生
Yes, sir.
卡車找到了
The truck's been found.
我們還不確定
Now we can't know for sure,
但似乎哈里發國沒有參與其中
but it looks as though ICO wasn't involved.
輻照器和銫都已找到
The irradiators and cesium were accounted for.
卡車偶然停在了
The truck was accidentally parked
達勒姆的一處醫療設備廠
at a medical device factory in Durham.
工頭沒有上報
The plant foreman never reported it.
所以我們暫時可以松口氣了
So we can relax for now, at least.
感謝大家的付出  謝謝你們
I just wanna thank you all for your efforts. Thank you.
總統女士  我明天一早就遞交辭呈
Madam President. You'll have my resignation in the morning.
諾拉
Nora...
今天這是極端情況
these were extraordinary circumstances today.
如果我們絲毫不容忍人為疏忽
What would our administration be
那我們政府成什么了
if we didn't allow for some human failings?
準備發布會  我們馬上上去
Get the presser going. We're coming up now.
關于艾哈邁迪
Concerning Ahmadi...
我們沒找到他
We didn't find him.
會找到的  你們可以的
You will. You can.
-你有什么提議  -我可以幫忙
- What are you offering? - Help.
如果您愿意  總統女士
If you'd like it, Madam President.
你能詳細說明一下今天早些時候的演習嗎
Can you elaborate on the drill earlier today?
演習時常進行
Well, drills happen all the time.
這是政府為了保證國家安全
It's part of the administration's ongoing efforts
做的不懈努力
to keep the country safe.
-是  但通常都會提前提醒  -那意義何在
- Yes, but there's usually a warning. - What's the point of that?
-下一位  -賽斯
- Who's next? - Seth.
你看檔案了嗎
Did you look at the file?
不用看
I didn't have to.
我希望一小時內
I'll expect your signature
收到你簽名的辭職信
on the resignation letter within the hour.
除非你選擇指出其他涉事的人
Unless you choose to implicate whoever else was involved.
你不配入主白宮
You don't deserve to be in the White House.
你和你丈夫都不配
Neither you nor your husband.
我本想祝你一切安好  但我覺得你不需要
I'd wish you the best, but I don't think you'll need it.
我相當確定你在私人機構也能干得很好
I'm fairly certain you'll do very well in the private sector.
我安排了周末跟簡·戴維斯的會面
I've scheduled a meeting with Jane Davis for the end of the week.
很好
Good.
還有  我之前就想說的
Also, I was going to mention this earlier,
凱茜對艾丹·麥卡倫非常好奇
but Cathy's been very curious about Aidan Macallan.
我已經轉移了她的視線  但...
I've thrown her off the scent, but...
凱茜不是問題  而是麥卡倫
Cathy's not the problem. The problem is Macallan,
還有那個縱容麥卡倫成為問題的人
and the person who allowed Macallan to become the problem.
基金募集到了超過了八萬
The foundation's raised over 80K.
安東尼于2016年3月15日進入1類捐贈名單
Anthony became status one on the donor list on March 15th, 2016.
莫雷蒂說那是她生命的最后一天
Moretti talked about it as, uh, the last day of her life
之后又改了口
before she corrected herself.
還有  時時刻刻陪著孩子
What else, spent every spare second with the kids.
他們還組裝卡丁車來著
They were building a go-kart.
本來就要完成了
They were pretty close to done.
-好吧  -還有呢
- Okay. - I got more.
-不用  我知道了  -你本想知道什么
- No, I got it. - What were you looking for?
沒什么
It's nothing.
-好吧  -怎么了
- Okay. - What?
你打算告訴我今天白宮發生了什么嗎
You wanna tell me what happened in the White House today?
不打算
No, I don't.
好吧  我一直等著跟你說點事
All right, I've been waiting to say something,
可我等得不想再等了
but I've waited and I don't want to wait anymore.
幫我留意下白宮的工作吧  在新聞部
Consider me for a job at the White House, in comms.
"去拿這個  幫我找那個  我要這個"
"Go get this. Find me that. I need this."
我受夠了
I'm tired of it.
你不提出  就會被人命令
If you don't ask, you get asked.
我開始意識到這點了
That's what I'm starting to realize.
我會幫你推薦的
I'll put a word in.
是嗎  這話什么意思
Yeah? Well, what does that mean?
意思是時機合適的話  我會提及你
It means that when the moment is right, I'll mention you.
沒錯  最終宣布后
Yes, whenever it happens...
這次任命便能打破最高法院的僵局
this appointment would break the court's deadlock
我們終于能繼續推進這次大選了
and we would get this election going again.
但請大家退一步想一想
But let's step back a minute...
-田納西州...  -你的鹽呢
- Tennessee... - Where's your salt?
-無論誰贏下田州  -水池右邊
- Whoever wins that state... - Right side of the sink.
這樣就取決于最后一個州
It's come down to one state:
俄亥俄州
Ohio.
一個州的選擇  將左右
One state is about to choose
下一任美國總統的人選
the next President of these United States.
那真是演習嗎
Was it really a drill?
這屆政府一貫喜歡搞閉門政治
This is an administration that operates behind closed doors.
知道嗎  今天發生了那么多事
You know, with everything that was happening today,
《先驅報》還來了一個記者
this reporter from the Herald came by.
什么
What?
他想寫東尼和基金的報道
Wants to do a story on Tony and the foundation.
他叫什么
What was his name?
戴維斯暗示她能幫我們找到艾哈邁迪
Davis implied she could help us track down Ahmadi.
我覺得我們該聽聽她要說什么
I think we should hear what she has to say.
她有一種氣質  對吧
She's got a quality about her, doesn't she?
令人著迷又害怕
Attractive and terrifying.
就像想撫摸紅尾狐的沖動
Like the urge to pet a red tail fox.
將軍遞交辭呈了嗎
The general offered his letter?
是的  但拒絕供出其他人
Uh, he did. And refused to implicate anyone.
你說得對  克萊爾  我們得和厄舍談談
You were right, Claire. We need to sit down with Usher.
他這周末正好要去北加州
Just so happens, he's going to Northern California this weekend
見一幫人
to meet with a group of men
討論我們國家的危機和未來
to discuss the crisis and the future of our country.
-你得受邀才能參加  -對  找他幫忙
- Well, you need to be invited to that. - Yes, let's get him in.
我知道這很顯然  但那總讓我受觸動
I know it's obvious, but it always strikes me.
沒有女人
No women.
那個時代不一樣
Well, it was a different time.
真可怕
Terrible.
戰爭還是時代的局限性
The war or the restrictions of the era?
都是
Both.
你知道我的態度
Well, you know my position.
我完全支持女性參戰
I'm all for women in combat.
虛驚一場
False alarm...
我很擔心你
I was worried about you.
我一直都擔心你  克萊爾
I worry about you all the time, Claire.
但我知道你不喜歡聽這種話
But I know that's not the kind of thing you like to hear.
馬克  進來
Mark. Come in.
-我們有很多要談  -總統女士
- We have much to discuss. - Madam President.
總統先生
Mr. President.
我確信你知道
As I believe you know,
我們昨天在白宮進行了演習
yesterday we had something of a drill here in the White House.
我知道大家都在好奇怎么回事
I know people are wondering what that was about.
是啊  除了你
Yes. Everyone except you.
本森法官的休會任命宣布儀式
The announcement of the recess appointment of Judge Benson
已經改到明天上午了
has been rescheduled for tomorrow morning.
很好  那...
Good. So...
我們可以進行選舉了
we have an election.
但你別想再靠所謂的
Which you will not be able to win
大選期間  在十月逆轉競選局勢的現象
"十月驚喜"贏得選舉
with another so-called October surprise.
-十月早就過了  -確實
- Well, we are way past October. - We certainly are.
據我所知艾哈邁德·艾哈邁迪仍有威脅
I understand Ahmed Al Ahmadi is still a threat?
是  但你也知道  他神出鬼沒
Yes, but he's so elusive, as you know.
很可惜你沒能抓到他
It's a shame you weren't able to capture him.
好吧
Well...
我相信機會
I believe that the opportunity
會自己跑到下任總統手中
will present itself to the next president,
無論總統是誰
whomever he may be.
如果威爾·康威勝選
If Will Conway wins the office,
我可以向你保證那會成為當務之急
I can assure you that'll be a top priority.
這恐怖氛圍得停止了
This terror has got to stop.
我已經占用你們太多時間了
I've taken enough of your time.
馬克  我想放點東西給你聽
Mark, I just want to play something for you.
只要一會兒
It'll only take a moment.
我對天發誓
I swear to God,
要是安德伍德往邊境派兵
if Underwood puts soldiers on those borders,
我第一個站出來讓軍人抗命
I'll be the first to tell them not to listen.
如果美國總統下達那種命令
If the President of the United States gives orders like that,
你就讓他早死...
you put him out of his--
行  不必再聽了
Okay. I don't need to hear anymore.
但  馬克
Oh, but, Mark...
后面更精彩
it gets so much better.
美國總統  最高法院大法官  國會議員  都有自己藏身的秘密地堡
最初的地堡被認為是在富蘭克林·羅斯福時期建造的
在冷戰時  艾森豪威爾總統在國會協助下修建了更多的地堡
這些足以抵御核武器襲擊的秘密地堡  其數量  地點均屬于國家機密
但幾十年來  媒體不斷搜集蛛絲馬跡  確認應該有40個左右這樣的地堡
大部分位于首都華盛頓周圍100英里內的山區
這些地堡除了異常堅固之外  有的面積也非常大  可以臨時充作空軍基地
白宮作戰室位于白宮西廂的地下室
而用于藏身的總統緊急行動中心(PEOC)則位于東廂的生活區下面
2011年奧巴馬在任時期  橢圓辦公室后院曾大興土木
對外稱是空調及電路維修  但很多媒體猜測可能是在擴建地堡